A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2 FA430
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
1966-1999
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund.
Harkness, Mary Emma Stillman, 1874-1950
Harkness, Edward Stephen, 1874-1940
Harkness, Charles W.
Harkness, Anna M. Richardson, 1837-1926
FA430
15 Cubic Feet 34 document boxes.
Arrangement note
Series 2 is arranged in the following subseries: 1 Author Files; 2 Correspondence; 3 Meetings; 4 Proposals; 5 Publicitity;, 6 Banking;, 7 Budget Files; 8 Financial.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for scholarly research, except where particular restrictions are noted.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Other Finding Aids note
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
Related Materials
See also:
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The Rockefeller Archive Center acquired a major portion of the Commonwealth Fund archives in 1986. Tranfers continue reguarly.
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Education, Rural; Medical research; Hygiene; Law; Child welfare; Child psychology; Medicine, Rural; Child mental health; Public welfare; Legal issues; Legal research; Mental health; Public health; War relief; Medical education; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; New York (State); New York (N.Y.); United States; Commonwealth Fund.; Columbia University.; Harkness, Mary Emma Stillman, 1874-1950; Harkness, Edward Stephen, 1874-1940; Harkness, Charles W.; Harkness, Anna M. Richardson, 1837-1926; Yale University.; Social Science Research Council.; Phillips Exeter Academy.; Harvard University.
- Author Files, 1
  - Beeson, Paul
    - 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Beeson, Paul - Contract, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Feedback, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Publications, 1980, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cloud, Preston
    - Book Reviews, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Party, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, 1985, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 8A)
    - Contract/Payments, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Promotion, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Reviews, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Royalty Statements, 1984-1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Subcontracting Expenses, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Friedman, Herbert
    - Book Reviews, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Contracts Foreign, 1966, 1970, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Contract/Payments, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Reception, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Reviews, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Royalty Statements, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Subcontracting, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Gowans, Sir James
    - Contract, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Proposal, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Harold Ober Associates
    - 1983-1984, 1986, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Peter Shepherd, 1986, 1989, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Hart, John F.
    - Book Reviews, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Contract/Payments, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1981, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Correspondences, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Digital Media - Floppy Disk, 1990-1993 (Box 30, Folder 31A)
    - Photographs & Transparency, 1985, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 32A)
    - Maps & Diagrams, 1985, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Marketing, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Party, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Party, 1991 April (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Party, 1991 May (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Party, 1999 May-July (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Publication, 1960, 1976, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Reviews, 1984-1985, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Royalties, 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Subcontracting, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Hoagland, M.
    - Book Reception, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Book Reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Captions, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Contract/Payments, 1983, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1992, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Introduction by Dr. Lewis Thomas, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Jacket Flap, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Original Proposal, 1983, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Reviews, 1983, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Royalty Statements, 1990-1995 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Subcontracting, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Lovelock, James
    - AGES of GAIA-Revised Version, 1994 June 22 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Contract/Payments, 1984-1985, 1987, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1989, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Foreign Contracts, 1988-1992, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous Pieces, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Promotion, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Royalty Statements, 1988-1995 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Toni Werbell - Publicist, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - McCarty, M.
    - Correspondence, 1982-1986, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Editing, 1983, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Foreign Contracts, 1986, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Parties, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Photographs, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 67A)
    - Proofs, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Reviews & Advertising, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Royalty Statements, 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Signed Contract, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - McFarlane, R.
    - Book Reviews, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Contract/Payments, 1984-1985, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Marketing, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984, 1990, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Proposal, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Reception, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Reviews, 1983-1984, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Royalty Statements, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Subcontracting, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Norton, W. W. & Company
    - Contract, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Edwin Barber, 1986-1990, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Thorne, Kip
    - Book Review, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Contract, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Contract/Payments, 1986-1987, 1990, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Foreword by Stephen Hawfins - Black Holes and Time Warps, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Foreword by Fred Seitz, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Illustrations, 1986, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Party, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Proposal, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Reviews, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Reviewers' Comments, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Royalty Payments, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Subcontracting, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Weatherall, Sir David, FA430
    - Contract/Payments, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Dedication, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Manuscript - Chapters 1-4, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Manuscript - Final, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Manuscript Final Correspondence, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Outline, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Party, 1993 Jan. 26 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Promotion, 1995 May 25 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Reviews, 1990-1995 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Royalty Payments, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - The Imperfect Instrument, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Who's Who, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Westbroek, Peter
    - Book Review, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - Contract/Payments, 1985, 1990, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - Foreign Contracts, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983, 1985, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - Permissions, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Proposal & Outlines, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Reviews, 1984-1990, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - Royalties, 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Subcontracting, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - The Moving Landscape - Life as a Geoloogical Force - Bringing Sciences Together, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - Life as a Geological Force - Bringing Sciences Together, 1990 June 13, 18 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Brochure
    - Annoucement, 1982-1986 (Box 12, Folder 124)
    - Request, 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 125)
    - 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 126)
    - Request for Updating Grant Information, 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 127)
    - Solicitions, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Contracts and Agreements
    - 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 129)
    - Signed, 1983-1986, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 130)
- Correspondence, 2
  - Annual Files
    - 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 132)
    - 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 133)
  - Alexander G. Bearn, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Envelope 134)
  - Book Program Declines, 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 135)
  - Committee Memos, 1987-1990 (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - Committee Reviews, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 137)
  - Karen Davis, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - Erichson, Robert, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - Donald S. Fredrickson, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 140)
  - June Goodfield, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 141)
  - Lynn Marqulis, 1986, 1989-1990, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 142)
  - Margaret E. Mahoney, 1986, 1989-1990, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 143)
  - Lady Jean Medawar, 1986, 1988-1990, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 144)
  - Maclyn McCarty, 1986, 1988-1995 (Box 14, Folder 145)
  - J. Robert Moskin, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 146)
  - David E. Rogers, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - Berton Roueche, 1986, 1988, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - Mary Lou Russell, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Frederick Seitz, 1986-1989, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Lewis Thomas, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 150)
  - Otto Westphal, 1986-1991, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 151)
  - Cynthia Woodcock/Andrienne A. Lindgren, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 152)
- Meetings, 3
  - Advisory Committee (Box 15)
  - 1983 April 16 (Box 15, Folder 153)
  - 1983 Sept. 24 (Box 15, Folder 154)
  - 1983 April 16, Dec. 11 (Box 15, Folder 155)
  - 1984 March 17 (Box 15, Folder 156)
  - 1984 Sept. 15 (Box 15, Folder 157)
  - 1985 March 23 (Box 15, Folder 159)
  - 1985 March 23 (Box 15, Folder 160)
  - 1985 Oct. 12 (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - 1985-1986 April (Box 15, Folder 162)
  - 1986 April 19 (Box 15, Folder 163)
  - 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 164)
  - 1987 April-July (Box 15, Folder 165)
  - 1987 May 16 (Box 15, Folder 166)
  - 1987 Oct. 17 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - 1988 May 7 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - 1988 Fall (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - 1989 Nov. 18 (Box 16, Folder 171)
  - 1989 (Box 16, Folder 172)
  - 1990 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - 1991 Feb.-Oct. (Box 16, Folder 174)
  - 1991 Oct. 5 (Box 16, Folder 175)
  - Alexander Bearn, 1988 Nov. 5 (Box 16, Folder 176)
  - Cosmopolitan Club - Cohn Library, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 177)
  - Final Meeting, 1993 Feb. 13 (Box 16, Folder 178)
  - Suzanne H. Heyd, 1988 Nov. 5 (Box 16, Folder 179)
  - Last Meeting Accomodations, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Last Meeting - Letters Sent, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Last Report, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - General Comments, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Guest List, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Manuscript Status, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Meeting Arrangements, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Thorne Reviews, 1993 Feb. 13 (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Weatherall, Reviews, 1993 Feb. 13 (Box 16, Folder 188)
- Proposals, 4
  - Ahrens, E. H., 1986 (Box 17, Folder 189)
  - Albert, Daniel, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 190)
  - Allen, Robert Day, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 191)
  - Ames, Genevieve, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 192)
  - Andrade, J. D., 1989 (Box 17, Folder 193)
  - Ayala, Francisco, 1983-1987 (Box 17, Folder 194)
  - Barghorn, Elso S., 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Basch, Paul F., 1983 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Bearison, David J., 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Bearn, A., 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  - Beitchman, J. H., 1981, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 199)
  - Benjaminson, M. A., 1983, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 200)
  - Bishop, J. Michael, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Blau, Eric, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 202)
  - Bonner, J. T., 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 203)
  - Bornstein, Marc H., 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 204)
  - Brennan, T. A., 1987, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 205)
  - Breuer, Hans, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Brewer, Richard D., 1983 (Box 18, Folder 207)
  - Brody, Barbara L., 1982, 1985, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 208)
  - Broeker, W. S., 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Burns, David M., 1988 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Buss, Leo W., 1984 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Calvin, W. H., 1987 (Box 18, Folder 212)
  - Carmen, Ira H., 1983 (Box 18, Folder 213)
  - Cassidy, C. M., 1984 (Box 18, Folder 214)
  - Cavalli - Sforza, Luigi, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 215)
  - Caws, Peter, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Chawla, K. K., 1983, 1986, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Chalmers, Thomas C., 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - Cohen, Jack S. and Portugal, Franklin H., 1983 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Cohen, Mark N., 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 220)
  - Cohen, Stanley, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 221)
  - Cornford, C.
    - 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 222)
    - 1986 (Box 19, Folder 223)
  - Cournand, Andre, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 224)
  - Crane, Loren, D., 1983 (Box 19, Folder 225)
  - Davis, B.
    - 1986-1989 (Box 19, Folder 226)
    - Proposal Outline, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 227)
    - Review, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Day, E. D., 1985 (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Denness, Bruce, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Dethier, Vincent G., 1984 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - Diamond, L., 1988 (Box 20, Folder 232)
  - Dobkin, R., 1985 (Box 20, Folder 233)
  - Dols, M. W., 1985 (Box 20, Folder 234)
  - Doolittle, W. Ford, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 235)
  - Dorwart, R. A., 1982-1982 (Box 20, Folder 236)
  - Drachman, V. G., 1984 (Box 20, Folder 237)
  - DuBois/Almon, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 238)
  - Duckworth, D. H., 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 239)
  - Dyer, B. D., 1984 (Box 20, Folder 240)
  - Editorial Resumes, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 241)
  - Eliason, M. J., 1989 (Box 20, Folder 242)
  - Elsasser, W. M., 1982 (Box 20, Folder 243)
  - Epstein, A. W., 1983 (Box 20, Folder 244)
  - Feinstein, Alvin. R., 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 245)
  - Feldman, Michael, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 246)
  - Ferris, Timothy, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 247)
  - Fisher, H. W., 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 248)
  - Fox, Renee C., 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 249)
  - Fredrickson, D. S.
    - 1980-1981, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 250)
    - 1988 (Box 21, Folder 251)
  - Friedberg, F., 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 252)
  - Gale, Robert P., 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 253)
  - Gallagher, H. G., 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 254)
  - Gerken, George M., 1984 (Box 21, Folder 255)
  - Glaser, R. J., 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 256)
  - Glassman, E., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 257)
  - Goebel, W., 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 258)
  - Goodfield, June, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 259)
  - Godding, P. A., 1989 (Box 21, Folder 260)
  - Goodwin, W. L., 1986 (Box 21, Folder 261)
  - Goran, M., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 262)
  - Gordon, M., 1985 (Box 21, Folder 263)
  - Green, Nancy R., 1986 (Box 21, Folder 264)
  - Greenberg, M. S., 1984 (Box 21, Folder 265)
  - Greenstein, G., 1984 (Box 21, Folder 266)
  - Golubic, Stjepko
    - 1985-1988 (Box 21, Folder 267)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 268)
  - Gunkel, Patrick
    - 1981-1983 (Box 21, Folder 269)
    - 1983 (Box 22, Folder 270)
  - Guth, Allan, 1984 June 11 (Box 22, Folder 271)
  - Hall, Diana L., 1974 (Box 22, Folder 272)
  - Hamming, R. W., 1988 (Box 22, Folder 273)
  - Hammond/Bingham/Ferris, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 274)
  - Han, Jian, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 275)
  - Harcum, E. R., 1986 (Box 22, Folder 276)
  - Harris, H.
    - 1985 (Box 22, Folder 277)
    - 1985 Nov.-Dec. (Box 22, Folder 278)
    - 1986 Jan.-Feb. (Box 22, Folder 279)
  - Harris, Victor, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 280)
  - Hasting, J. W., 1987 (Box 23, Folder 281)
  - Heinrich, B., 1973, 1979-1980, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 282)
  - Hershely, Daniel, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 283)
  - Hiatt, H. H., 1984 (Box 23, Folder 284)
  - Hobson, J. A., 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 285)
  - Hormann, E., 1988 (Box 23, Folder 286)
  - Horne, R. A., 1983, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 287)
  - Horowitz, N. H., 1985 (Box 23, Folder 288)
  - Horowitz, O., 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 289)
  - Houston, C. S., 1986 (Box 23, Folder 290)
  - Hu, Qi, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 291)
  - Hurlburt, F., 1989, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 292)
  - Itzkoff, S. W., 1984 (Box 23, Folder 293)
  - Jacob, F., 1986 (Box 23, Folder 294)
  - Jacobs, C., 1986 (Box 23, Folder 295)
  - Jacobs, P. H., 1986 (Box 23, Folder 296)
  - Jolly, Alison, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 297)
  - Kagan, Jerome, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 298)
  - Kandel, Eric R., 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 299)
  - Katz, Sir Bernard, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 300)
  - Kaufman, C. L., 1986 (Box 24, Folder 301)
  - Kaufman, S. R., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 302)
  - Kelly, L. C., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 303)
  - Kendrick, Bryce, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 304)
  - Kiecolt - Glaser, J., 1985 (Box 24, Folder 305)
  - Kilborne, B., 1986 (Box 24, Folder 306)
  - Kingdon, Jonathan, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 307)
  - Kiple, K. F., 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 308)
  - Klien, K., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 309)
  - Klien, Wolfgang, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 310)
  - Klienman, A., 1985 (Box 24, Folder 311)
  - Koelzer, S. M., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 312)
  - Kraus, E. B., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 313)
  - Kunitz, S. J., 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 314)
  - Laden, N., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 315)
  - Lambert, D. R., 1984 (Box 24, Folder 316)
  - Lanouette, W., 1985 (Box 24, Folder 317)
  - Layon, A. J., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 318)
  - Leader, Robert W., 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 319)
  - Lechtenberg, R., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 320)
  - Lederberg, Josh, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 321)
  - Lee, David W., 1986 (Box 24, Folder 322)
  - Lee, Richard V., 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 323)
  - Leppington R. T., 1989 (Box 24, Folder 324)
  - Lerch, Irving A., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 325)
  - Levin, E., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 326)
  - Lingappa, B. T., 1986 (Box 24, Folder 327)
  - Logan, J. L., 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 328)
  - Logan, J. W., 1987 (Box 25, Folder 329)
  - Long, C. A., 1986 (Box 25, Folder 330)
  - Lopez, Carlos, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 331)
  - Lovejoy, Thomas E., 1983 (Box 25, Folder 332)
  - Lowenstein, H. A., 1985 (Box 25, Folder 333)
  - Lowry, Robert, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 334)
  - Mahdavi, Kamal, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 335)
  - Maiorana, V. C., 1983 (Box 25, Folder 336)
  - Manthey, Michael J., 1984 (Box 25, Folder 337)
  - Marvin, D. A., 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 338)
  - Mehrtens, S. E., 1987 (Box 25, Folder 339)
  - Medawar, Sir Peter, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 340)
  - Milke, V., 1989 (Box 25, Folder 341)
  - Miller, Warren B., 1983 (Box 25, Folder 342)
  - Miller, Wayne C., 1989 (Box 25, Folder 343)
  - Mills, Robert, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 344)
  - Mock, D. W., 1985 (Box 25, Folder 345)
  - Mogus, Mary Ann, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 346)
  - Moreno - Black, G., 1985 (Box 25, Folder 347)
  - Musto, David F., 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 348)
  - Netsky, Martin G., 1983 (Box 25, Folder 349)
  - Norton, Bryan G., 1984 (Box 25, Folder 350)
  - Nussenzweigs, R. S., 1982, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 351)